Robert Maxwell

Junior Full-Stack Developer

1920 19 Avenue NW Calgary, AB. PH: 403-383-2297 Email: robinix585@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/kilanga-maxwell-fullstackdeveloper/
Portfolio: https://joyful-mermaid-e72c12.netlify.app/

Objective

Experienced Junior Full-stack Software Developer with competencies in design, development, testing and database management of software systems. Professional experience with working in various platforms and programming languages. Conversant with modern development tools and procedures. Highly capable of effective self-management during independent projects, as well as in collaboration with productive teams.

Experience

Aug. 2021 - Present

Full-Stack Developer • Smag Graphique LATAM

- Proprietary RFID Software Development with Microsoft .NET and C#.
- Upgraded legacy code base for higher performance and efficient maintainability.
- Improved existing API with added functionality.
- Designed intuitive user interface according to client specifications.
- Installation and testing of software application on label converting machines.
- Database design, development, and management.
- Documentation of all technical specifications.
- Web and desktop development using React, Javascript, Graphql and MongoDB.

Feb. 2022 - Jun. 2022

Web Developer (Part Time) • IPS Projects EPCM

- Design of UI/UX for proposed company website.
- Assisted in developing and implementing system design and architecture.
- Web and desktop development using Angular and .NET frameworks.
- Provided code tests and website maintenance.

Education

Diploma in Information Technology - Software Development Southern Alberta Institute of Technology

Jan. 2019 - May, 2021

Diploma in Mechanical Engineering Technology – Design & Automation Southern Alberta Institute of Technology

Sept. 2015 - Sept. 2017

Skills

- HTML/CSS/JavaScript
- React
- Typescript
- Microsoft .NET
- C#
- Angular
- Java
- PHP
- SQL
- WordPress
- Graphql
- MongoDB
- Git
- Jira
- Express
- Docker
- AWS
- DevOps

Continuous Development Programs

Harvest Talent Incubator Coding Bootcamp • Harvest Builders Oct. 2022 – Nov. 2022

Immersive Data Analytics Program • BlackTech Career Hub Sep. 2022 – Present